Here the
quarter one result of ICC Lombard General Insurance Company has been declared.
Guys, what kind of result will be seen, we will
discuss it in detail in today's
video and a decline of about 1% was seen
in the company today and the company
provides insurance, the company General Insurance does
insurance related work here, the
company provides financial services and if we talk about the market cap, then the
market cap of the company is 60000397 crores
and the current price is running around 1352
which is trading around the high here, the
high that the company had set in 52 weeks, if we
talk about the stock price, then it is around 37
while the industry is 51 and see, the company Aarohi is seen to be a little cheap
and this is a great company, the
book value of the company is seen
here at ₹10 and if we talk about
dividend, then here around 74 percent
points can be seen, if we talk about the
debt, then the debt is equal to zero, the
company's holding on the company is seen at 48 here
and the company does not even have any reserve,
which
Despite the price not being negative, it is
a bit more expensive as per the gram number. At the same time, the
net cash flow is also visible here in the mines.
According to the score of Ad Pitrosh of the company, it
is best for the long term and in the short term, it is
seen to be a bit negative.
Fundamentals and returns over 3 March, the
company gave a return of 25% and PPS
is 36, so very good fundamentals but there is
no reserve, the company does not have debt
and cash flow in the mines and if we talk about it, it is
quite expensive as per the gram number.
Talking about sales, guys sales have been
seen increasing from the previous quarter.
In the last quarter, where the sales were 45 to 19
crores, which has increased
to 4600.94. Talking about expenses, the
expenses have decreased here as
compared to the previous quarter. Operating profit was
seen increasing here.
In the last quarter, an
operating profit of 355 crores was seen in the mines, which
increased  OPM has reached 491 crores, there has also been an
increase here, if we talk about
net profit, then in the last quarter
where a net profit of 437 crores was seen,
which has come down to around 390 crores, the
tax which was 24% in the last quarter has
increased to 25% and if we look at it, there was a
decline in profit
in this quarter and if we talk about the share on running, then
₹890 has decreased to around ₹795, let us
also see what kind of holding of investors is being seen, the
holding of investors in scooters has decreased here.